…Kang So-mang is going viral online.
It has also been confirmed
that the video was indiscriminately shared
with all her acquaintances
and family members in her phone contacts
at the time of the incident.
Furthermore, the individual responsible
for sharing the video
had been identified as the victim…
- Stay still!
- No! I told you no, okay?
…there is one critical suspicion
that has come to the forefront
in the video leak.
Mo, who has been indicted
for the murder of the dentist couple,
is now under suspicion
of also killing their son, Ko Se-hun,
the defendant in Kang's case.
Some have begun to draw the conclusion
that Kang's sexually explicit video…
Inmate 407 is waking up.
…against Mo and her family.
The police are thoroughly investigating…
Inmate 407!
And that's where we lost her.
We're reviewing
surveillance cameras around the scene,
but since it was rush hour,
it made it very difficult to identify her.
She could be anywhere by now.
I would've never expected
she'd pull something like this.
It's not at all like her.
This is her MO.
An Yun-su has been our murderer
since we first laid eyes on her.
Let's see what we got.
You made it.
- Yeah.
- Here. Have a seat.
Oh, I thought it was scheduled for 5:00,
but I guess you got started already.
As you know,
I'm here from the Ministry of Justice.
Locating An Yun-su is our duty as well.
But earlier, you neglected
your duty to keep an eye on her.
Right, where were we?
Has the digital camera been restored?
I'm afraid the restoration
will take some time.
Mo Eun's current status?
Oh, well, fortunately, she made it.
Though I don't know if "fortunately"
is the right word to use.
And do we have positive identification
of the intruder at An Yun-su's residence?
It was Ko Dong-uk,
Ko Se-hun's grandfather.
The same one who attacked Mo Eun then?
At the hospital?
We have to be careful
when we go after him.
Otherwise, the media will let us have it.
He lost his son,
his daughter-in-law, and now his grandson.
Doesn't that demonstrate
how deep the resentment is?
Deep indeed.
In fact, his fury is so deep,
he won't hold the funeral
until the killer is caught.
If we can apprehend her,
then everything will begin to make sense.
Until then, I would appreciate
any cooperation to help track her down.
Much more than…
TV news won't do you any good.
Nothing so urgent that a stabbing victim
should be concerned.
I'm thinking it wasn't a mistake,
choosing the power room.
You did it so An Yun-su could escape.
They've fully mobilized to bring her in.
Nothing for the asshole
who hit me and stabbed you though.
It's ridiculous.
Who was it, huh?
How could you have not seen them?
Who attacked us?
GYEONGGI BUKBU PROVINCIAL POLICE
Review the hospital again,
but widen the search.
And don't be too narrow.
Report any suspicious behavior.
You got it.
MURDERER'S SISTER,
KANG'S WILD PRIVATE LIFE
HIDDEN TRUTH BEHIND ILLICIT VIDEO LEAK
GANGAN DAILY JOURNALIST HONG SE-YEONG
Hong Se-yeong.
Well, hello there, Mr. Baek.
What's the pleasure?
- Your article. Tell me where you got it.
- Which article?
Not to mention you had
the exclusive scoop on the kid too.
Tell me. Who gave you the info?
Oh, yeah.
I wondered the same thing,
but they said they wanted anonymity.
And a call came through
from a blocked number.
I'd love to know who it is too, honestly.
The little jerk always calls up
like a whistleblower, all high and mighty.
It's personal,
if you ask me though.
- A lady's voice?
- No, a man's voice.
Somehow I feel like there's more
to this tipster. Isn't there?
If you thought it was a lady's voice,
An Yun-su was your guess, right?
Send me a screenshot
of the time the tipster called.
Oh, sure. I can do that.
I'll send it to you,
but if you find out who it is,
tell me too.
We got an emergency call
from An Yun-su's phone.
- Pinged the location?
- Ko Dong-uk's property.
112, what's your emergency?
Are you in danger right now?
I need help.
Are you able to give me your location?
If Ko Dong-uk has hurt An Yun-su,
what's next?
What do we do?
Offer to resign.
'Cause the old bastard found An Yun-su
before we did.
Come in.
112, what's your emergency?
Are you in danger right now?
I need help.
Are you able to give me your location?
Hello?
Are you there?
That was an emergency call
from An Yun-su's phone,
and data shows the phone
is somewhere around here still.
Tell me, where's An Yun-su?
Huh?
Are you suggesting I did this to her?
Where were you on the morning of the 13th?
I always take the dog
for his daily walk early in the morning.
So can someone confirm that?
You can go to the park.
I'm sure there's someone there
who will provide you with an alibi.
Yes, but you did go to
An Yun-su's house on the 12th.
I did.
I rang the doorbell,
and she was there. She opened it.
And then there appeared to be a struggle,
which made her run away.
The woman is the suspected killer
of my grandson.
I had questions I wanted to ask.
But it looks like she panicked
and ran off.
How did you find her house?
How did you know in the first place?
She wasn't named a suspect
on the news yet,
so how did you even know that?
Whose tip? Who told you,
and what did they say?
We found An Yun-su's phone!
It wasn't locked or anything.
No pin or passcode.
Wait, she came here on purpose, then?
And looks like she stayed
for about 20 minutes.
What is she trying to do?
So can you see this has nothing
to do with me now?
All right, sir.
Is anything missing?
Nothing's been stolen.
I need you to be honest with me.
About what?
Are you still playing dumb?
She ran away from you in a panic,
but now she's back,
and of her own volition.
On top of that, she also managed
to bring the investigation team here.
Who was it?
Who was it that told you
An Yun-su was the suspect?
And that Mo Eun was in the hospital?
You heard that too. Right?
I have no idea what you mean.
Sir!
Her jacket.
I wanna smoke. Do you mind?
DAEHO BOXING GYM
Make sure to get pics.
Over there as well. Okay?
Did something happen?
You said you didn't know where she was.
Instead, you've given her a hideout?
I didn't know.
I haven't been here in over a year.
So then how would
An Yun-su know she could use it?
I mentioned it once. I guess she found it.
Come on up and see.
Come and see what she's done.
What's this supposed to be?
What do you think it is?
She recreated the murder scene?
Bragging about her crime.
Almost like she wants us to see it.
- If it was her, there's gotta be a reason.
- To what end?
There's no more here
than a painting of the victim dead.
- What if she's trying to send a message?
- Wake up, will you.
It's An Yun-su's phone.
Found it at the home of Ko Dong-uk.
Here.
THIS IS WHAT YOU'VE BEEN DOING?
Is that clear enough for you?
I don't believe it.
SENDER: AN YUN-SU
Is this… An Yun-su's number?
Hold on.
Every photo here just further
implicates her as Ko's killer.
No.
Couldn't these have been sent
by someone pretending to be her?
Every photo was taken by somebody else.
We don't know who took them,
or where they came from, so--
So someone pretending
to be her also painted that?
What other explanation is there?
Up until now, she's begged us
to believe she wasn't a murderer.
The evidence is against her.
There's more than enough
to prove that An Yun-su is the killer.
Mo Eun is aware that I didn't kill him,
and she knew
Ko Se-hun was dead before I did.
I don't know how she knew that,
but I need to find out.
Mo Eun must know something, right?
- Could you let me see her, please?
- You can't.
And I'm sure you understand
why you can't see her.
There's something going on here
we're not getting.
Why is she suddenly behaving like this?
Why would anyone do something like this?
Does it make any sense to you, Mr. Baek?
So she ran off with my phone
'cause she knew I had her photos.
NEW EMAIL
AN YUN-SU'S DIGITAL CAMERA RESTORED
The cause of death was stab wounds
to the right side of the neck,
piercing the carotid artery
four times in total.
There are marks that indicate
he was strangled with both hands.
Hold on. Every photo here just
further implicates her as Ko's killer.
Is it because
you had something to do with it?
Don't tell me you made
some kind of arrangement with Mo Eun.
Let's go see Mo.
You want to know why
An Yun-su's doing this
and what she knows?
Let's find out.
Let me ask the questions this time, okay?
Let me take the lead.
I look forward to it.
DELETE
AUTHORIZED PERSONNEL ONLY
Oh. Coffee is allowed in, or so I thought.
These aren't.
Oh, right.
- She's still on the mend.
- Of course, I'm aware.
Can you please avoid saying anything
to provoke her, if possible?
Can we go in now?
I'll be using this
to record our conversation.
Do I have your consent?
It has to be verbal.
Yes.
Oh, would you mind removing the handcuffs?
I'll be waiting outside.
I'm Jang Jeong-gu.
Attorney for Ms. An Yun-su.
I know.
Because you're always around.
I know the recital is keeping you busy,
but you mustn't neglect your hands.
It's getting cold.
Don't forget your lotion.
Prosecutor Baek and
Jang Jeong-gu are questioning Inmate 407.
I suggested you should also be present,
but Inmate 407 refused.
How is Mo Eun doing these days?
Surgery went well, they said.
However,
Mr. Jang and the prosecutor
appear to be questioning her now.
Isn't that something
you should be present for?
Mo Eun doesn't want me there, so…
I'll just follow up with Mr. Jang later.
Ms. An doesn't seem like
the person I know lately.
Must be something going on there.
The investigative team
thinks it's just a challenge.
- I'm afraid if things get worse, then--
- Get worse?
How much worse can they get?
We have to find her.
Please tell me where she might've gone.
But I don't know. Really.
Why did you do this to her?
Of all the people, why did you choose her?
Honestly, she's an easy mark.
That's why Prosecutor Baek
was also convinced that it was her.
She comes off as
transparent.
And that's something
people take advantage of.
So it was easy for you, then, I suppose.
- You'd exchange a confession to have--
- You think we had an arrangement.
Don't you?
Well, didn't you?
These were sent from the detention center.
Ms. An's unrelenting anxiety? I'm guessing
you had something to do with it.
There's not much time left.
Don't try and get smart now.
What kind of situation
did you force her into?
THIS IS WHAT YOU'VE BEEN DOING?
YOU DON'T HAVE TIME
She's become a shadow of herself,
but you kept pushing her to the edge,
making her come look for you. Why?
She said that you knew
that she didn't kill Ko Se-hun.
What exactly do you know?
More than you're letting on.
Has he told you
the photo she took looks different?
Or is prosecutor Baek keeping it from you?
What is she talking about?
It's different.
You're right.
The photo recovered from her camera
doesn't match the autopsy results.
But the one you swallowed must have,
and so did the painting.
- Mr. Baek.
- All right, fine.
Let's pretend what you said could be true.
Couldn't it also be true
that An Yun-su purposefully sent you
that photo before coming?
I think she's clever enough to have
tricked you and is manipulating us.
An easy mark? Transparent?
How can you say it wasn't her…
…when there's so much evidence
to the contrary?
There's more to her than meets the eye.
How do you know? You just talked
through a wall for a few days.
Your bias is showing.
Precisely.
I'm biased.
And that's how it's been
since the moment I saw her.
But I think you can say the same,
Mr. Baek.
An Yun-su was spotted
at the Hongseo University Gallery.
It's Lee Ki-dae's memorial exhibition.
It looks like she went there
to see her husband's work.
I don't know what she was thinking,
going there in the middle of all this.
So the photo didn't match
the autopsy results.
Anything else you're hiding?
You asked me
if I thought she was innocent.
I wanted to believe it
because I just couldn't be sure.
What about you? You still convinced?
You're not sure, are you?
Maybe An Yun-su wasn't even the killer
to begin with, like she said.
Maybe none of this would've ever happened
if I hadn't sent her to prison
in the first place.
You're starting to think
that's a possibility.
You're having doubts, right?
Mr. Baek!
There's nothing wrong with having doubts.
Having doubts is totally fine.
I mean, it's nothing important,
but it's like those American TV shows.
The cops always start with the family.
I have to get back home now.
I just wanted to thank you for everything.
Means a lot to me.
What makes you so certain
that it was me?
What do you even know?
That's what I want to believe.
An Yun-su.
She didn't kill Ko Se-hun.
That's her pure nature.
LEE KI-DAE: MEMORIAL EXHIBITION
SOKOBOAKO, THE LOST PATH
GIFT OF JIN YOUNG-IN, CHOI SU-YEON
BREAKING NEWS: CONFESSION VIDEO
OF AN YUN-SU GOES VIRAL
I admit that I killed my husband.
And at the detention center,
Mo Eun and I came to an arrangement
that never should've happened.
The deal was she would confess
to my husband's murder.
In return,
I would kill Ko Se-hun when released.
I accepted this horrible offer
only 'cause…
'cause I wanted to be with my daughter.
It was a selfish act, plain and simple.
When I got out,
I tracked Ko Se-hun's movements.
But then, when…
when I finally met him face-to-face,
I couldn't kill him.
I couldn't bring myself
to take another life
just so that I could keep on living.
I have decided to publicly reveal
my crime like this
because the investigative team
has decided to turn
a blind eye to certain evidence.
Evidence that a third party was present
on the day Ko Se-hun was killed.
They'd rather just make me the murderer.
There is dashcam footage
showing this third party
leaving Ko Se-hun's house.
The team has this video
in their possession.
Why would she do that?
OCTOBER 7
LIGHTS TURNED ON AT 8:00 P.M.
I killed my husband. Yes.
But I am not Ko Se-hun's murderer.
I am willing to accept the punishment
for the crime I committed…
but there must also be punishment
for the boy's murderer.
SOKOBOAKO
GIFT OF JIN YOUNG-IN, CHOI SU-YEON
I killed my husband. Yes.
But I am not Ko Se-hun's murderer.
I am willing to accept the punishment
for the crime I committed,
but there must also be punishment
for the boy's murderer.
An Yun-su,
is this what you were trying
to communicate?
Criminal Investigation Team Two, yes?
Yes. Thanks for reaching out.
- Gyeonggi Bukbu Police Station, yes?
- Hurry up.
We are not able to answer
those questions right now.
Ms. An, what are you trying to do?
JUNGDONG GENERAL HOSPITAL
So desperate for revenge
that you'd make
another person do it for you.
But also,
you did everything you could
to save that girl.
GU ***-YEONG / F
Come in.
She wanted to thank you
for saving her life.
I'm gonna be watching, okay?
Thank you…
for saving my life.
We've…
met.
It was a video call.
Precisely.
I knew it.
Your sister
talked about you a lot.
You were close?
Not in the beginning.
I skipped school and stuff.
I'm not a good student.
But then,
she was friendly.
When we became deskmates,
she talked to me first.
That's how we got close.
My baby sister had a lot to say.
She always loved to talk to me.
But when it mattered most,
I couldn't help her, so…
- There he is.
- Get the shots.
Later! Later! Okay!
Oh. Hey, Mr. Baek.
You didn't actually cover it up, did you?
Huh?
We did not.
We really didn't!
Afternoon, sir.
There's no evidence of a third party.
She's lying.
I know.
We have to find An Yun-su.
That's the first thing.
Then we'll understand what this is about.
Is it desperation or possibly…
Afternoon.
Who let him in?
I'm here for my client, Ms. An Yun-su.
You're here for what?
I told you I'm here for my client.
I found her alibi. I'm finally able
to prove she didn't kill Ko Se-hun.
But now she's confessed
to her husband's death.
Can you make sense of that, Mr. Baek?
Come on, Mr. Jang.
How can you still believe her?
She admitted to killing her husband
and made a deal with a murderer.
Come on, Mr. Baek. What's your opinion?
Are you still so confident
An Yun-su is the killer?
Well?
An Yun-su mentioned evidence.
Is it legitimate?
If that's the case,
why would you be hiding it?
All due respect,
but who do you think
is being truthful about this?
She basically confessed to the murder
of her husband just to tell us this.
Only cause no one listens
when you whine about how wronged you are.
You know something.
What is it?
Mr. Baek.
I don't want to intrude, but…
Mr. Jang, Sop has gone missing.
What?
They're saying that she's been kidnapped.
A kid saw it happen.
They said that an old man was there
and took her away.
What do we do? Huh?
Ko Se-hun used to gamble online a lot.
He lost the tuition to his tutoring center
and even started borrowing
from upperclassmen.
So then,
he started deepfaking pics
of girls from school to sell.
Videos were the next step.
He started filming.
There was a kid
who was his assistant.
The boy who visited you.
He would help with Ko Se-hun's cats.
He made him install
a pet cam on his phone.
Ko Se-hun would pay him
to deepfake pictures of girls,
then blackmailed him.
Made him his gopher.
But he said
he saw it.
Se-hun's murder.
Listen to me, okay?
I saw Ko Se-hun…
get murdered.
And who did it?
KANG SO-MANG, SEXUAL ASSAULT CASE
KO SE-HUN, PROTECTIVE DETENTION NO. 5